The One Where It All Began (Pilot)
얘기할 것도 없어
같이 일하는 동료일 뿐야
There's nothing to tell.
It's just some guy I work with.
무슨 소리
come on You want to.. going out with the guy.
남자랑 데이트하는 거잖아
그 남자 이상이 있는 거라구
There has got to be something
wrong with him.
등에 혹이라도 난 거야?
혹에 털까지 났나?
All right, Joey.
Be nice.
So does he have a hump
and a hairpiece?
그 사람 분필 먹는구나?
Wait, does he eat chalk?
칼 같은 사람을 만났을까봐
걱정이야
I don't want her to go through
what I did with Carl.
다들 흥분할 거 없어
이건 데이트도 아냐
Okay, everybody relax.
This is not even a date.
두 사람이 함께 식사를 하고
섹스는 안 하고 헤어지는 거라구
It's just two people going out
to dinner and not having sex.
나한테는 데이트 같은데?
Sounds like a date to me.
고등학교 때였는데, 내가
식당 한 가운데 서있는 거야
I'm in high school,
in the cafeteria...
그것도... 홀딱 벗고
...and I realize l' m totally naked.
나도 그런 꿈 꿨어
I've had that dream.
그런데 아래를 내려다보니까
전화가 있는 거야
Then I look down and I realize
there is a phone...
거기에!
...there.
- 그럼...
- 그렇다니까
-lnstead of--
-That's right!
그런 꿈은 안 꿔봤어
Never had that one.
그런데 갑자기 전화가 울리기
시작하는 거야
All of a sudden,
the phone starts to ring.
어찌할 바를 모르겠더라
내게 시선이 집중됐으니까
What do I do?
Everyone starts looking at me.
시선 받아본 게 처음이야?
They weren't looking at you before?
어쨌든 전화를 받기로 했지
Finally, I figure
I'd better answer it.
전화를 건 사람은 엄만데
And it turns out it's my mother.
그게 정말 이상하단 얘기야
엄만 절대 전화를 않거든
Which is very, very weird
because she never calls me.
안녕
Hi.
쟤가 저렇게 인사하면
콱 죽어버리고 싶어
He says, " Hello, "
I want to kill myself.
괜찮아, 오빠?
You okay?
누군가 내 목에 손을 집어넣고
내장을 잡아채서
I feel like someone pulled my
intestine out of my mouth...
입 밖으로 꺼내서
목에 돌돌 마는 기분이야
-...and tied it around my neck.
-Cookie?
쿠키 먹을래?
캐롤이 오늘 짐을 가져갔대
Carol moved her stuff out today.
- 커피 타줄게
- 고마워
-Let me get you some coffee.
-Thanks.
그만, 내 기를 청소할
생각은 하지 말아 줘
No, don't!
Stop cleansing my aura.
- 그래도...
- 내 기를 그냥 두란 말야
-Just leave my aura alone, okay?
-Fine, be murky.
그럼, 우울한 기를 즐겨
난 괜찮아, 솔직히
캐롤이 행복했으면 좋겠어
-I'll be fine. I hope she'll be happy.
-No, you don't.
거짓말
당연히 거짓말이지
날 버리고 간 매정한 여잔데
No, I don't.
T o hell with her. She left me!
캐롤이 레즈비언인 거
정말 몰랐어?
You never knew she was a lesbian?
그래, 몰랐다
No! Okay?
왜 항상 그걸 묻는 거지?
Why does everyone
keep fixating on that?
자기도 몰랐다는데
내가 어떻게 알았겠어?
She didn't know.
How should I know?
나도 레즈비언이면 좋겠다
Sometimes I wish I was a lesbian.
목소리가 너무 컸나?
Did I say that out loud?
부모님께 말씀드렸는데
이해해주시더라
I told Mom and Dad last night.
They took it pretty well.
그래? 그럼 새벽 3시의
신경질적인 목소리는 누구지?
Oh, really?
So that hysterical phone call
from a woman sobbing...
이제 손자 보긴 글렀다고
한 노인네는 누구냐구?
... " I'll never have grandchildren, "
was what? A wrong number?
미안해
Sorry.
괜찮아, 로스
Look, you' re feeling
a lot of pain right now.
지금 많이 고통스러울 거야
화도 나고 상처를 입었지
You' re angry.
You' re hurting.
이럴 때 해답이 뭔 줄 알아?
Can I tell you what
the answer is?
스트립바에 가는 거야!
Strip joints!
넌 독신이잖아
넘치는 호르몬을 해결해야지
Hey, you're single.
Have some hormones.
난 독신이 싫단 말야, 알아?
다시 결혼하고 싶어
But I don't want
to be single, okay?
I just want to be married again.
누구 백만 달러 없어?
And I just want a million dollars!
레이첼?
-Rachel?
-Oh, Monica! Thank God!
세상에, 모니카
다행이야
너희 집에 갔는데 없더라
I went to your building...
커다란 망치를 든 남자가
여기 있을 거래서 와본 거야
...and a guy with a hammer
said you'd be here, and you are.
- 커피 드려요?
- 카페인 없는 걸로요
-Can I get you some coffee?
-Decaf.
얘들아, 여긴 레이첼이야
링컨 고등학교 동창
Everybody, this is Rachel,
a Lincoln High survivor.
이쪽은 친구들이야
챈들러, 피비, 조이
This is everybody.
Chandler and Phoebe...
...Joey.
Remember my brother, Ross?
그리고 우리 오빠 로스 알지?
그럼
Sure!
- 안녕
지금 말할 거야, 아님
들러리들 올 때까지 기다릴래?
You want to tell us now, or are we
waiting for four wet bridesmaids?
그래, 결혼 30분전쯤부터
얘기가 시작돼
Well, it started about
a half-hour before the wedding.
선물이 잔뜩 쌓여있는 방에
앉아있는데
I was in the room
with all the presents...
...and I was looking at this
really gorgeous Limoges gravy boat.
엄청나게 큰 수프 그릇이
보이는 거야
그걸 보니까 갑자기...
When all of a sudden--
카페인 없죠?
그런 생각이 들었지
Sweet ' N Low?
배리보다 그 수프 그릇에
기대고 싶어진 거야
I realized I was more turned on by
this gravy boat than Barry.
그러더니 갑자기 정신이 번쩍
들면서 그런 생각이 떠올랐어
I got freaked out,
and it hit me:
배리가 감자 머리 아저씨처럼
생겼다는 생각이...
How much Barry looks
like Mr. Potato Head.
그 동안 난 배리가
낯이 익다고 생각했거든
I always knew
he looked familiar, but....
어쨌든...
난 방을 뛰쳐나와서 생각했지
I had to get out of there,
and I started wondering...
"내가 왜, 누굴 위해서
결혼을 하려는 걸까?"
... "Why am I doing this, "
and "Who am I doing it for? "
어쨌든, 그런데 어디로
가야할 지 모르겠더라구
I didn't know where to go,
and I know we've drifted apart...
너랑은 연락 안 한 지
오래 됐지만
이 도시에 사는 사람은
너 하나 뿐이었어
... but you' re the only person
I know here.
근데 난 결혼식에 초대도
안 했어?
-Who wasn't invited to the wedding.
-I hoped that wouldn't be an issue.
지금 그게 문제가 아냐
저 남자가 여자한테
파이프 오르간을 사줬는데
I guess he bought her the pipe organ,
and she's really not happy about it.
여자는 별로 좋아하지 않나봐
참치냐, 샐러드냐?
"T una or egg salad!
Decide! "
결정해!
크리스틴이 먹는 걸로 줘요
"I'll have whatever
Christina's having. "
아빠, 죄송해요
그 사람이랑 결혼 못해요
Daddy, I just--
I can't marry him.
죄송해요
I' m sorry.
I just don't love him.
그를 사랑하지 않아요
저한테는 중요한 문제예요
Well, it matters to me!
머리를 잡고 있어야
안 떨어지지
" If I let go of my hair,
my head will fall off. "
저런 바지 입으면 안 되지
She should not be
wearing those pants.
계단으로 밀어버려
Push her down the stairs!
계단으로 밀어버려,
밀어버려!
Push her!
Push her down the stairs!
그렇지!
아빠, 제 말 들어보세요
Come on, Daddy, listen!
평생을 사는 동안 다들 저한테
넌 신발이야라고 해요
All my life, everyone's
always told me, "You're a shoe! "
넌 신발이야, 넌 신발이야
"You' re a shoe! "
그런데 갑자기 제가 생각하죠
신발이 되기 싫다면?
What if I don't want to be a shoe?
지갑이 되고 싶다면?
아님, 모자가 되고 싶다면?
What if I want to be a purse?
Or a hat?
모자를 사달란 얘기가 아녜요
제가 모자란 얘기라구요
No, I don't want you
to buy me a hat!
은유도 몰라요?
It's a metaphor, Daddy!
뭐가 문젠지 알겠다
You can see where he'd have trouble.
아빠, 제 인생이에요
Look, Daddy,
it's my life.
어쩌면 여기서 모니카랑
지낼지 몰라요
Well, maybe I'll just stay
here with Monica.
모니카랑 여기 있기로
얘기가 끝났나 보네
I guess we've established
she's staying with Monica.
어쩌면 그게 제 결정이겠죠
Well, maybe that's my decision.
어쩌면 아빠 돈은
필요 없을 거예요
Maybe I don't need your money.
잠깐
어쩌면 이라고 했잖아요
Wait!
I said maybe!
좋아, 숨을 들이마셔
Just breathe. That's it.
좋은 것,
침착한 걸 생각해봐
T ry to think of nice, calm things.
장미꽃 위의 빗방울,
고양이 수염
Raindrops on roses
And whiskers on kittens
초인종 소리와 썰매 소리,
장갑 낀 손가락
Doorbells and sleigh bells
And something with mittens
끈으로 예쁘게 묶은...
La la la something
And noodles with string
훨씬 좋아졌어
I' m all better now.
내가 도와줬지
I helped.
좋은 쪽으로 생각해봐
This is probably for the best.
독립해서 네 인생을
살아가게 된 거라구
Independence. Controlling your life.
The whole hat thing.
그리고 말야
You can always come to Joey.
필요한 게 있으면
이 조이한테 찾아와
나랑 챈들러는 복도 건너에
사는데, 거의 나 혼자 있어
Me and Chandler live across the hall.
He's away a lot.
조이, 찝쩍대지 마
오늘 얘 결혼식 날이야
Stop hitting on her!
It's her wedding day.
결혼식 날엔 찝쩍대지 말라는
법이라도 있어?
Like there's a rule, or something?
내가 가볼게
I got it.
다시는 그러지 말아요
소리가 끔찍하네요
Please don't do that again.
It's a horrible sound.
폴입니다
It's Paul.
벌써 6시 반이야?
Oh, God, is it 6:30?
Buzz him in.
들어오라고 해
- 폴이 누구야?
- 와인 담당 폴?
-Who's Paul?
-Paul, the wine guy?
어쩌면...
Maybe.
잠깐, 와인 담당 폴이랑
가짜 데이트하는 거야?
Your " not a real date"
is with Paul, the wine guy?
- 데이트 신청했어?
응
-
-He finally asked you out?
-Yes!
일기라도 써야겠네
It's a " Dear Diary" moment.
- 레이첼, 취소하라면 할게
- 아냐, 난 괜찮아
-Rach, I can cancel.
-Please, go, I'll be fine.
오빠, 괜찮아?
오빠랑 있어 줄까?
Ross, are you okay?
Do you want me to stay?
그럼 고맙지
That'd be good.
- 정말?
- 아니, 와인 담당 폴인데
-Really?
-Go on! It's Paul, the wine guy!
와인 담당이 뭐야?
Does he sell it, drink it?
와인 파는 사람?
잘 마시는 사람?
Or he just complains a lot?
들어와요, 폴
여긴...
Hi, come in!
Paul, this is...
친구들이에요
얘들아, 폴이야
...everybody.
Everybody, this is Paul.
- 안녕, 폴
- 와인 담당
-The wine guy.
-I didn't catch your name. Paul?
미안하지만 이름을 못 들었는데
아마 폴이었죠?
금방 나올게요
제가 잠깐, 잠깐...
I'll be right back.
I've just gotta go--
산책이라도 하게?
A-wandering?
옷 갈아입는 거야
Change.
앉아요, 잠깐만요
Sit down.
Two seconds.
속눈썹을 네 개나 뽑았어
징조가 안 좋은데
I just pulled out four eyelashes.
That can't be good.
중요한 정보 하나 줄게요
Hey, Paul, here's a tip.
모니카는 목을 계속
문질러 주는 걸 좋아해요
She really likes it when you
rub her neck in the same spot...
아주 빨개질 때까지요
... until it starts to get red.
닥쳐, 조이
Shut up, Joey!
레이첼, 오늘 계획 있어?
What are you up to tonight?
아루바로 신혼여행 가려고
했었는데, 지금은 없어
I was supposed to be headed
for Aruba on my honeymoon...
...so, nothing.
맞아, 신혼여행 못 갔지?
Right. You' re not even
getting your honeymoon.
그게 아니라, 아루바는...
Although, Aruba.
This time of year?
매년 이맘때면 거긴...
T alk about your...
도마뱀 천지가 된다구
... big lizards.
어쨌든, 오늘밤 혼자 있기
싫으면...
If you don't want
to be alone tonight...
조이랑 챈들러가 새 가구
조립하는 거 도와주기로 했어
...Joey and Chandler are
helping me with my furniture.
그래, 신나 죽겠다
We' re very excited about it.
고맙지만 오늘은 나가서 좀
돌아다닐 거야
Thanks. But l' m just
going to hang out here.
- 피곤한 하루였어
- 그래, 그렇게 해
-It's been a long day.
-Oh, sure.
피비, 우리 도와줄래?
Pheebs, wanna help?
그랬으면 좋겠는데,
그러기 싫어
I wish I could,
but I don't want to.
사랑은 뜨거운 여름비
사랑은 숭고한 예술
Love is sweet as summer showers
Love is a wondrous work of art
하지만 당신의 사랑은
당신의 사랑은...
But your love
Oh, your love, your love
거대한 비둘기
Is like a giant pigeon
고 놈이 당신 가슴을
후려치고 가죠
Crapping on my heart
라라라...
고맙습니다
Thank you.
라라라...
받침대인지 뭔지를 옆부분에
부착할 때는
I' m supposed to attach a bracket-y
thing to the side things...
작은 나사 한 뭉치를
사용하라고 써있는데
... using a bunch of these
little worm guys.
받침대인지 뭔지도 없고
나사 한 뭉치도 없고
I have no bracket-y thing.
I see no worm guys whatsoever...
다리 감각도 없어
...and I cannot feel my legs.
- 이건 책장 같은데
- 근사하다
-We got a bookcase.
-It's beautiful.
이게 뭐야?
What's this?
니은 자 받침 같다고 할 수 있지
I would have to say
that is an L-shaped bracket.
어디다 놓냐구?
-Which goes where?
-I have no idea.
나도 모르지
- 책장은 다 됐어
- 다 끝났어
-Done with the bookcase.
-All finished.
캐롤이 제일 좋아하는 맥주야
This was Carol's favorite beer.
항상 캔으로 마셨지
그때 알아봤어야 되는데
She always drank it out of the can.
I should have known.
야, 야, 야
너 술 주정 시작하면
그냥 갈 거야
-Start with that, we're out of here.
-Please don't spoil all this fun.
지금 기분을 깨지 마
로스, 하나만 물어보자
Let me ask you.
캐롤이 가구고 오디오고
TV고 다 가져갔는데
She got the furniture,
the stereo, the good TV.
넌 뭘 가져갔어?
What did you get?
- 너희가 있잖아
- 맙소사
-You guys.
-You got screwed.
- 네 인생이 불쌍하다
- 맙소사
- 세상에
- 알아요, 내가 바보였죠
-Oh, my God.
-I know. I' m such an idiot.
치과에 일주일에 너댓번 씩
갔을 때부터 알아봤어야 돼요
I should've known when she went to
the dentist five times a week.
그래서 이가 남아났겠어요?
I mean, how clean can teeth get?
우리 오빠도 많이 힘들어해요
My brother's going through that.
불쌍해서 못 봐주겠어요
어떻게 이겨냈어요?
How did you get over it?
부인이 소중히 여기던 걸
망가뜨리는 것도 좋을 거예요
He might accidentally
break something valuable of hers.
- 말하자면...
- 다리요?
-Say her--
-Leg?
그것도 좋은 방법이겠군요
That's one way of doing it.
I went for the watch.
전 시계를 택했죠
- 부인 시계를 망가뜨렸어요?
- 네
You actually broke her watch?
제가 썼던 해소법은...
The worst I ever did was shred
my old boyfriend's favorite towel.
그 남자의 수건을 갈가리
찢는 거였어요
- 큰 손해는 없었겠네요
- 당연하죠
-Steer clear of you.
-That's right.
배리, 미안해
정말 미안해
Barry, l' m sorry.
I am so sorry.
자기가 양말 신고 자는 걸
싫어해서라고 생각하겠지만
You probably think it's about making
love with your socks on, but it isn't.
그게 아냐, 그런 게 아니고
나 때문이야, 내가...
It's about me.
And I just--
안녕, 응답기가 또 끊어졌어
어쨌든...
The machine cut me off again.
Anyway....
있잖아, 나도 알아
당신 부인이 될 여자는
정말 행운이라는 거
I know that some lucky girl is going
to become Mrs. Barry Finkel.
하지만 난 아냐
난 아니라구
But it isn't me.
It's not me.
사실 난 지금 내가
누군지도 모르겠어
Not that I have any idea who "me" is
right now, but you just--
어쨌든 자기는 다른 여자...
난 이혼했어
I' m divorced.
26살에 이혼남이야
-l' m only 26, and l' m divorced!
-Shut up!
- 닥쳐라!
- 제발 닥칠래?
그거 한 시간 걸린 거야
That only took me an hour.
네가 알아야할 게 있어
We haven't had a relationship
that's lasted longer than a Mento.
조이와 나는 너처럼
질기게 사귀는 걸 본 적이 없어
넌 한 여자와 4년을 만났어
You have had the love of a woman
for four years.
친밀함을 4년이나 나누더니
결국 실연의 상처만 안았어
Four years of closeness and sharing,
after which she ripped your heart out.
그래서 우린 그 짓을 안 해
That is why we don't do it!
말이 이상하게 샜다!
I don't think that was my point!
뭐가 제일 두려운 줄 알아?
IKnow what's scary? What if there's
only one woman for everybody?
나한테 맞는 여자가 하나
뿐이라면 어떡하지?
나한테 맞는 여자는 달랑
하나밖에 없다면?
I mean, what if you get one
woman, and that's it?
내 경우엔 내 여자가 다른
여자를 찾아간 셈이잖아
Unfortunately, in my case,
there was only one woman for her.
무슨 헛소리야?
여자가 하나 뿐이라니
What are you talking about?
One woman.
나한테 맞는 아이스크림은
하나 뿐이란 소리 같잖아
That's like saying there's only
one flavor of ice cream.
똑똑히 들어, 아이스크림
종류는 엄청나게 많아
Let me tell you something.
There's lots of flavors out there.
록키 로드, 쿠키 도우,
빙 체리 바닐라!
Rocky road and cookie dough
and bing cherry vanilla.
호두, 땅콩을 넣은 거나
거품 아이스크림도 있지
You can get them with jimmies
or nuts or whipped cream.
얼마나 잘된 일이야?
It's the best thing
to happen to you!
넌 결혼까지 했잖아
철딱서니 없게 무슨 소리야?
You got married.
You were like, what, 8?
현실세계에 온 걸 환영한다
스푼을 집으라구
Welcome back to the world.
Grab a spoon!
솔직히 배가 고픈 건지
여자가 그리운 건지 모르겠어
-I don't know if I'm hungry or horny.
-Then stay out of my freezer.
내 냉장고엔 얼씬도 마
집사람이 날 버리고 간 후로...
Ever since she walked out on me....
왜요?
What?
국수 가락을 뱉어버리고 싶어요?
You wanna spell it out with noodles?
아뇨, 이런 얘긴 다섯 번은
만나야 할 수 있을 거예요
It's more of a fifth date
kind of revelation.
그럼 다섯 번째 데이트가
있는 건가요?
So there's going to be
a fifth date?
없는 거예요?
Isn't there?
아뇨, 있을 거예요
Yeah, yeah.
I think there is.
무슨 얘길 하려고 했죠?
What were you going to say?
집사람이 날 떠난 후로
Ever since she left me...
제대로 해본 적이 없어요
... I haven't been able to perform...
섹스 말예요
...sexually.
이런, 맙소사
정말 미안해요
Oh, God!
I' m so sorry.
괜찮아요
물을 뿜으라고 한 얘기는
아니었을 거예요
Being spit on is probably
not what you need right now.
얼마나 됐는데요?
How long?
2년이요
-Two years.
-Wow.
시계 망가뜨린 거 잘한 거예요
I' m glad you smashed her watch.
우리 다섯 번째 데이트
할 수 있는 건가요?
So you still think you might
want that fifth date?
네
Yeah.
Yeah, I do.
그래요
나 조니는 찰스를 남편으로 맞아...
We are gathered here
to join Joanie Louise Cunningham...
...and Charles.
Chachi, Chachi, Chachi...
...in the bonds of holy matrimony.
저것 봐, 조니는 차치를 사랑해
그게 다르다구
See!
But Joanie loved Chachi.
That's the difference.
스푼을 집으라고?
"Grab a spoon. "
내가 스푼을 집은 지
얼마나 됐는지 알아?
Do you know how long it's been
since I grabbed a spoon?
나라고 스푼을 집고 싶지
않은 줄 알아?
Do the words, " Billy, don't be
a hero, " mean anything to you?
얘기 잘 들었어
Great story.
But I gotta go.
이제 가봐야겠어
안드레아와 약속 있어
I got a date with Andrea.
Angela. No, Andrea.
안젤라! 안드레아!
누구지?
안드레아는 수다쟁이
안젤라는 고양이 키워!
Andrea's the screamer.
Angela has cats.
고마워
그럼 줄리다, 간다!
Right, thanks. It's Julie.
I' m out of here.
생각해보라구
Here's the thing. Even if
I could get it together enough...
이 충격에서 벗어나 여자한테
데이트 신청을 한다고 쳐
...to ask a woman out...
누구한테 해야 하지?
...who am I going to ask?
버팀목이 필요할 때
내 이름을 불러요
내가 달려갈게요
버팀목이 필요할 때...
대단하지 않니?
Isn't this amazing?
I've never made coffee in my life.
내 손으로 커피 타보긴
이번이 처음이야
정말 대단하다
-That is amazing.
-Congratulations.
축하한다
이제 커피도 타니까
뭐든지 할 수 있을 거야
If I can make coffee,
there isn't anything I can't do.
도미노가 쓰러지듯이
후루룩 되는 게 아냐
I think it's, "lf I can invade Poland,
there's nothing I can't do. "
기왕 시작한 거
웨스턴 오믈렛도 만들어줄래?
If you feel like you have to make
a Western omelet or something....
근데 오늘 아침은
별로 배가 안 고프다
Although, actually
I'm really not that hungry.
이런! 참견쟁이들이 와있군
Oh, good.
Lenny and Squiggy are here.
- 좋은 아침
-Good morning.
- 안녕
- 안녕, 친구
-Morning.
-Morning, Paul.
- 안녕, 폴
- 폴 맞죠?
-Hello, Paul.
-Hi. Paul, is it?
고마워요
-Thank you so much.
-Stop.
- 고마워요
- 아니에요
어젯밤은 생일 같고
졸업식 같기도 하고
Last night was like
all my birthdays, both graduations...
영화 주인공이 된
기분이에요
... plus the barn-raising scene
in Witness.
- 나중에 얘기해요
- 그래요
We'll talk later.
고마워요
Thank you.
진짜 데이트가 아니라고?
That wasn't a real date.
진짜 데이트 때는 도대체
뭘 하는 건데?
What the hell do you do
on a real date?
- 닥치고 탁자나 제자리에 놔
- 알았어
Shut up and put my table back.
좋아, 난 일하러 가야겠다
숫자를 입력해야지
I've got to get to work.
If I don't input those numbers,
it doesn't make much of a difference.
그래봤자겠지만
너희 모두 직업이 있어?
So, like, you guys all have jobs?
그럼, 직업이 있지
그래서 물건도 사는 거고
Yeah, we all have jobs.
That's how we buy stuff.
그래, 난 배우야
-Yeah, l' m an actor.
-Have I seen you in anything?
내가 봤을 수도 있겠네?
아닐 거야
주로 지역 방송이거든
I doubt it.
Mostly regional work.
아니, 피노키오 재방송하면
볼 수도 있어
Unless you saw the Wee One's
production of Pinocchio...
...at the little theater
in the park?
어쨌든 일은 하잖아
It was a job!
"제페토 할아버지,
저 진짜 꼬마가 됐어요"
" Look, Geppetto.
I' m a real live boy. "
아무리 놀려봐라
-I will not take this abuse.
-You' re right, l' m sorry.
맞아, 미안해
옛날에 나무 인형이었을 때...
Once I was a wooden boy
A little wooden boy
둘이 잘 봐둬
You should both know
that he's a dead man.
저 녀석 이제 죽었어
챈들러...
Oh, Chandler!
오늘은 좀 어때?
How are you doing today?
Sleep okay?
푹 잤어?
배리한테 얘기했어?
Did you talk to Barry?
I can't stop smiling.
계속 웃음이 나오네
정말 그렇구나
입이 귀에 걸릴 만큼 좋았나봐
I see that. You look like you
slept with a hanger in your mouth.
그래
그이는 정말...
I know.
He's just so....
- 너랑 토니 사이 기억나지?
- 그럼
-Remember you and T ony Demarco?
-Oh, yeah.
그거랑 비슷해
비슷한 감정이야
Well, it's like that.
With feelings.
큰일났구나
-Wow, are you in trouble!
-Big time!
난리 났지!
내 웨딩드레스 입어
거의 새 거야
Want a wedding dress?
Hardly used.
우리 둘 다 정신 차리자
I think we're getting a little
ahead of ourselves.
좋아
나 그만 일어나야겠다
I'm going to get up, go to work,
and not think about him all day.
일하러 가야지
그이 생각은 그만할 거야
아님 그냥 일어나서
일하러 가든가...
Or else I'm going to get up
and go to work.
행운을 빌어줘
-Wish me luck!
-What for?
왜?
그거 하러 가야지
일자리 구하는 거...
I'm gonna go get one
of those job things.
안녕, 모니카
-Hi, Monica.
-Franny, welcome back.
프래니, 돌아왔구나
플로리다는 어때?
-How was Florida?
-You had sex, didn't you?
너 남자랑 잤구나?
어떻게 알았어?
-How do you do that?
-I hate you.
너무한다
난 늙은 숙모랑 씨름하는 동안
넌 데이트나 하고 다니다니
I' m pushing my aunt through
Parrot Jungle, you' re having sex.
누구야?
So, who?
폴 알아?
You know Paul?
- 와인 담당 폴?
응
-
Paul, the wine guy?
Yeah, I know Paul.
그럼, 알지
내가 아는 것처럼
너도 폴을 안단 말이지?
You mean, you know Paul
like I know Paul?
그걸 말이라고 해?
나한테 고마워해야 돼
What?
I take credit for Paul.
나 만나기 전에는 2년 동안
섹스 한번 못했거든
Before me, there was no snap in his
turtle for two years.
당연히 수작 거는 거였지
Of course it was a line.
왜?
왜 그런 짓을 하는 건데?
Why would anybody
do something like that?
뭔가 그럴듯한 대답을
기대할 텐데 미안하구나
I assume we want an answer
more sophisticated than:
침대로 끌어들이려고
"T o get you into bed. "
남자 미워, 싫다구!
I hate men.
그러면 안돼
Don't hate. You don't want
to put that out into the universe.
그건 우주의 법칙에
어긋나는 거야
근데 왜 나야?
Is it me?
나한테 무슨 표시 같은 게
있어서
Is it like I have some sort of
beacon that only dogs...
정서적으로 문제가 있는
남자들만 끌어당기는 거야?
...and men with emotional problems
can hear?
이리 와, 발 이리 줘
Come here.
Give me your feet.
난 좋은 사람이라고 생각했어
I just thought he was nice, you know?
수작 거는 걸 몰랐단 말야?
I can't believe
you didn't know it was a line.
무슨 일 있었게?
-Guess what?
-You got a job?
일자리 구했어?
무슨 소리야?
난 아무 것도 할 줄 몰라
Are you kidding?
I' m trained for nothing.
면접을 열두 군데나 봤는데
다 날 비웃더라
-I was laughed out of 1 2 interviews.
-You're surprisingly upbeat.
근데 넌 놀랄 만큼
즐거워 보인다?
조안 앤 데이빗 부츠를 반값에
사면 너희도 그럴걸
You'd be too,
if you found these boots on sale...
... 50% off.
네가 날 모르는구나
How well you know me.
옛날의 내가 아냐, 난 이제
직업도, 부모님도 필요 없어
They' re my
" I don't need a job...
나한텐 근사한 부츠가 있으니까
... I've got great boots" boots.
어떻게 샀어?
-How did you pay?
-Credit card.
신용카드로
그건 누가 갚는데?
And who pays for that?
아빠
My father.
꼭 이래야 하는 거니?
난 언제든 독립할 수 있어
Is this really necessary?
I can stop charging any time.
평생을 부모님께 의지해서
살 순 없잖아
You can't live off your parents.
알아
그래서 결혼하려고 한 거야
I know that.
That's why I was getting married.
너무 보채지 마
홀로서기가 쉽진 않을 거야
Give her a break.
It's hard being on your own.
고마워
Thank you.
천만에, 내가 이 도시에 처음
왔을 때가 14살이었어
I remember when I first
came to this city, I was 1 4.
엄마가 자살하고 의붓아빠는
감옥으로 돌아갔지
Mom had killed herself,
stepdad was in jail.
여기 처음 왔을 때
아는 사람이 아무도 없었어
I didn't know anybody here.
그러다 백색증 걸린 남자랑
살게 됐는데
I ended up living with this albino
guy who was cleaning windshields.
항만 관리위원회 건물에서
유리를 닦는 사람이었지
그 사람도 자살해버리고
And then he killed himself.
난 아로마 테라피를 배우게 됐어
나도 네 기분 잘 알아
Then I found aromatherapy.
So I know exactly how you feel.
이 시점에서 네가 할 말은...
The word you're looking for is:
'어쨌든'이야
"Anyway.... "
- 좋아, 준비됐어?
- 모르겠어
-You ready?
-No, how can I be ready?
이건, 비행기에서 낙하산도 없이
뛰어내라는 거랑 똑같아
" Ready to jump out of the plane
with no parachute? "
- 난 못해
- 할 수 있어
-I can't do this.
-I know you can.
난 못해
-No.
-You made coffee, you can do anything.
커피도 만드는데
다른 걸 못하겠어?
잘라, 잘라, 잘라!
Cut. Cut. Cut.
내 기분 알아?
You know what?
I think we can leave it at that.
카드 없이 살 수 있을 것 같아
상징적이긴 하지만
-lKind of a symbolic gesture.
-Rachel, that was a library card.
그건 도서관 카드였어
잘라, 잘라, 잘라...
'잘라'라는 말을 잘 들으면
물건 깎아줄 때 하는 말 같아
If you listen closely, you can hear
a thousand retailers scream.
좋았어
현실세계에 온 걸 환영해
Welcome to the real world!
거지같긴 하지만
맘에 들 거야
It sucks.
You're gonna love it.
다 끝났다
That's it.
Are you going to crash on the couch?
오빠, 소파에서 잘 거야?
아니, 가끔은 집에 가줘야지
-No, I gotta go home sometime.
-Are you gonna be okay?
- 괜찮겠어?
응
-
잠깐, 바닥에 이게 떨어졌네
Look what I just
found on the floor.
뭐야?
What?
폴의 시계야
That's Paul's watch.
Just put it back where you found it.
그냥 있던 곳에 둬
좋아
Oh, boy!
All right.
- 두 사람 다 잘 자
- 잘 자
-Good night, everybody.
-Good night.
미안
-l' m sorry. Have it, I don't want it.
-Split it?
- 아냐, 먹어
- 너 먹어, 난 별로야
나눠 먹을까?
- 그래
- 좋아
있지, 넌 모르겠지만
고등학교 다닐 때
You probably didn't know this,
but in high school...
널 좋아했었어
... I had a major crush on you.
알아
I knew.
알았어?
You did?
난 네가 날 모니카 네 괴짜
오빠로만 생각하는 줄 알았어
I figured you thought
I was Monica's geeky brother.
그랬어
I did.
있잖아...
Listen, do you think...?
나의 연약한 감수성을
보여주고 싶지는 않지만
T ry not to let my vulnerability
become a factor here.
어쩌면 말야, 가끔
데이트 신청해도 괜찮겠니?
Do you think it would be okay
if I asked you out sometime?
그래, 어쩌면...
Yeah.
Maybe.
좋아
Okay.
어쩌면 신청할지도 몰라
Okay, maybe I will.
- 잘 자
-Good night.
잘 가
See you.
잠깐, 왜 그래?
Wait, wait.
What's with you?
방금 스푼을 집었거든
I just grabbed a spoon.
-I can't believe what l' m hearing.
-Can 't believe what I'm hearing
지금 무슨 말을 하는 거야?
지금 무슨 말을 하는 거야
- 그러니까 내 말은...
-What? I said--
- What? I said
그만 좀 할래?
-Would you stop?
-Was I doing it again?
- 내가 또 그랬어?
- 그래!
Yes!
네 엉덩이가 괜찮다는 거지
근사하다는 건 아냐
I said you had a nice butt.
It's just not a great butt.
네가 직접 보기 전 까지
함부로 평가하지마
-You won't know a butt if it bit you.
-There's an image.
상상이 된다
커피 더 마실 사람?
Would anybody like more coffee?
네가 탄 거야, 아님
서빙만 하는 거야?
You made it,
or you're serving it?
- 서빙만 하는 거야
- 그럼 한 잔 줘
-l' m just serving it.
-I'll have a cup of coffee.
얘들아, 또 꿈 얘기다
이번엔 라스베가스야
IKids, new dream.
I' m in Las Vegas.
아가씨, 커피 더!
Miss, more coffee?
죄송하지만, 저분께
커피 좀 갖다 주세요
Could you give this
to that guy over there?
어서요, 고마워요
Go ahead.
Thank you.
미안해, 라스베가스?
Sorry.
Okay, Las Vegas.
그래, 라스베가스에서
I' m in Las Vegas.
난 라이자 미넬리야
I' m Liza Minnelli....